

Highly skilled front-end web developer with over 4 years of experience creating visually stunning and responsive websites. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Svelte JS, with a strong understanding of UX/UI principles. Experienced in developing custom WordPress themes and plugins, with a deep understanding of the WordPress ecosystem. Strong collaborator with excellent communication skills and a passion for creating intuitive user experiences.

CONTACT

ADDRESS

Maadi, Cairo, Egypt

PHONE

+201097671386

EMAIL

me.abdelfatah@gmail.com

WEBSITE

www.abdelfatax.com

FREELANCING

WordPress Developer

Letterlust.studios | 2022 - present

- Developing Plugins and fix smtp related issue
- Working with their clients

ABDELFATAH AHMED

WEB DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Web Developer

Saint Andrew's Refugees Services | Aug 2020 - present

- Developing and implementing website security protocols to protect the organization's data and online presence.
- Leading the design, development, and maintenance of the organization's website and related web applications.
- Designed and developed email campaigns

Progam's Officer

Saint Andrew's Refugees Services | Feb 2019 - Aug 2020

- Developing, implementing, and managing programs and initiatives that align with the organization's mission and goals.
- Participating in fundraising and development efforts, including grant writing and donor cultivation, to ensure continued program funding and sustainability.

Drop-in & Emergency Response Coordinator

Saint Andrew's Refugees Services | Jan 2018 - Feb 2019

- Coordinating drop-in services, ensuring that the space is welcoming, clean and organized, and that staff and volunteers are available to assist clients.
- Responding to emergencies, coordinating emergency shelter, food, clothing and other resources for individuals affected by an emergency.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science, Major in Computer Software

Cairo University | 2017

Certified Cisco Network Associate

American University in Cairo | 2018

SKILLS

- Web Design
- Front-end coding
- Custom databases
- User Interface/User
 Experience
- Design Thinking
- Front-End Web Dev
- IT Troubleshooting
- Unix Systems & servers
- Open-Source Support